Ankit Kumar Roshan

(akr.99799@gmail.com, +91 89497 05320)

Linkedin Github Portfolio

Overview

Passionate front-end developer with 2 years of industry experience in web application development. Involved in the core team, contributing to all phases of product development that include definition, design, scoping, planning, implementation, and testing of new features.

Work Experience

Appointy IT PVT LTD, Bhopal — Software Developer — August 2021 - PRESENT

- Provide clean and efficient code review within the team.
- Collaborate with internal teams to develop, enhance and fix product features, ensuring the best possible user experience.
- Work in an Agile-driven environment, effectively maintaining project timelines and utilizing available resources.
- Optimize code to reduce application latency and enhance performance.
- Optimize web accessibility throughout the application.

Appointy IT PVT LTD, Bhopal — Software Developer Intern — May 2021 - July 2021

- Developed a feature that displays the respective location in search results and Google Maps when a customer searches for a zip code.
- Developed and optimized web components.
- Gained experience in unit testing and end-to-end testing of the application to measure its effectiveness.

Skills

- Reactis
- TypeScript, JavaScript
- HTML, CSS
- GraphQL, React-relay
- Git
- Material-UI, Formik, Yup validation
- Jest, Cypress.io

Education

Vellore Institute Of Technology, Vellore — BTech

July 2017 - July 2021, Vellore

Electronic And Communication

CGPA: 7.8

Personal Work

• Covid tracker- Link